- 梅格 - 好啊
- Meg. - Hi.
- 你和乔一起猎鬼了 - 是啊 有一段时间了
- You were hunting with jo? - Yeah, for a while now.
那群傻瓜现在已经熔了那把枪了
The mooks have melted down the gun by now.
我听到的可不是这样的啊
Well, I hear differently.
如果你还想继续
And if you are still set on the insane task.
疯狂的猎杀任务的话 我们就得这么干
Of killing the devil, this is how we do it.
在《凶鬼恶灵》第33章里 那个女孩儿贝拉
In chapter 33 of "supernatural, " there was that girl bela.
她从你那里偷了科尔特
She stole the colt from you,
然后她说过把它给了莉莉丝 还记得吗
And then she "said" she gave it to lilith, remember?
- 是的 - 那你知道她说谎了 对吧
- Yeah. - Well, you know she lied, right?
- 她从来没有把它交给莉莉丝 - 你说什么
- She never really gave it to lilith. - What?
贝拉把科尔特给了一个叫克劳力的恶魔
Bela gives the colt to a demon named crowley.
克劳力
Crowley?
欢迎有能力的影视爱好者加入我们字幕组
加入仅凭个人兴趣爱好 没有任何金钱实质回报
你是彭德尔顿先生吧
Mr. Pendleton, I presume.
我是克劳力
The name's crowley.
在我的谈判中
I-in my negotiations, I was, uh,
我是和一位非常年轻性感的女士做的交易啊
Dealing with a very young, attractive, uh, lady.
这个我知道
Yes. I know.
但是你 贪心的家伙
But you, piggy banker…
你是一条大鱼
You…Are a big fish.
我想亲自来完成这个交易
And I wanted to do you the honor of sealing this deal personally.
但她说这个交易需要以吻来结尾
But she said the deal would be sealed with a kiss.
确实如此
That's right.
不 我的意思是 她
No, I mean, she's …
你自己选择
Your choice.
你可以保留60年来根深蒂固的憎恶同性恋情结
You can cling to six decades of deep-seated homophobia.
或者放弃它
Or just give it up.
紧急援助你的可怜的岌岌可危的银行
And get a complete bailout of your bank's ridiculous incompetence.
这件事只是
There are just things …
我数一
Going once…
不 我不这么认为
No, I don't think so.
二
Going twice …
好吧 我同意
All right! all right.
不
No!
找到他了
Got him.
恶魔克劳力正在做交易
The demon crowley is making a deal.
正当我们说话的时候
Even as we speak, it's…
已经完成了
Going…Down.
完成了
"Going down"?
对的
Right.
好吧 只是不要跟丢他
Okay, huggy bear. Just don't lose him.
我不会跟丢他的
I won't lose him.
太恶心了
Damn you.
好好享受这恶心的财富
Enjoy the obscene wealth.
10年后我来看你
See you in 10 years.
我跟着他了
I followed him.
不是很远 但是
It's not far, but…
墙被巫术分隔着
…It's layered in chian warding magic.
我进不去
I can't get in.
知道了 你做得很好 我们这就过去
That's okay. You did great. We'll take it from here.
谁啊
Yeah?
你好 我的车坏了 我需要帮忙
Hello? My car broke down. I-i need some help.
我们马上下来
We'll be down in a minute.
晚上好 靓妞
Evening, pretty lady.
别那么拘谨当这里是自己家
Get yourself on in here.
我只是需要打个电话
I just need to make a call.
你不需要打电话 宝贝
You don't need to call anyone, baby.
我们就是你需要的唯一帮助
We're the only help you're ever gonna need.
你知道吗
You know what? I…
我觉得我还是应该等在我的车旁
I think I should wait by my car.
说了你要留在这里
We said get your ass in here.
干的不错 乔
Nice work, jo.
谢谢夸奖
Thanks.
好的 一起走吧
Okay. Shall we?
你是克劳力 对吧
It's "crowley, " right?
看来你们还是找到我了
So…The hardy boys finally found me.
等候多时了
Took you long enough.
你们知道这小毛毯会带给你们什么
Do you have any idea how much this rug costs?
为了这个 对吧
This is it, right?
这就是你们要的
This is what it's all about.
我们需要谈谈
We need to talk.
就我们三个
Privately.
这到底是搞什么东西
What the hell is this?
知道我能把这玩意儿埋多深吗
Do you know how deep I could have buried this thing?
完全没理由让你们谁知道
There's no reason you or anyone.
这东西还存在
Should know this even exists at all.
除非我告诉你
Except that I told you.
你告知我们
You told us?
谣言 讥讽 消息不胫而走
Rumors, innuendo… Sent out on the grapevine.
为啥
Why?
为啥要告知我们这一切
Why tell us anything?
我想让你们拿它去对付路西法
I want you to take this thing to Lucifer.
打他个脑开花
And empty it into his face.
好吧
Okay.
为何你这样要他死
And why exactly would you want the devil dead?
这就是所谓
It's called…
生存
Survival.
不过我忘了 你们俩最多也就是有点用的智障
But I forgot … you two, at best, are functional morons.
对 有点用的智障
Yeah, you're functioning…Morons.
低能
Mor…
路西法不是恶魔 忘了么
Lucifer isn't a demon, remember?
他是天使
He's an angel …
以憎恨人类闻名的一个天使
An angel famous for his hatred of humankind.
对他而言 你们俩只是 污秽的脓包而已
To him, you're just… Filthy bags of pus.
若他真是这么看待你们的话
If that's the way he feels about you…
那他又会如何看待我们呢
…What can he think about us?
但是他诞生了你们
But he created you.
我们只能算是他的奴隶
To him, we're just servants.
有价值的材料而已
Cannon fodder.
如果路西法决定消灭人类
If Lucifer manages to exterminate humankind…
接下来就是我们了
…We're next.
所以
So…
帮帮我
Help me.
让我们回去那个简单 又比现在好过的日子
Let's all go back to simpler, better times.
回到那个性本善的日子
Back to…When we could all follow our natures.
该死 我都在推销了
I'm in sales, damn it.
那么你们是怎么想的
So, what do you say?
如果
What if…
我把这玩意儿给你们
I give you this thing…
你们去灭了恶魔
And you go kill the devil?
好
Okay.
很好
Great.
你不会正好也知道
You wouldn't happen to know.
那些恶魔在哪儿 是吧
Where the devil is, by chance, would you?
礼拜四
Thursday.
伯蒂斯告诉我
Birdies tell me…
他有个在密苏里州迦太基的约会
He has an appointment in carthage, missouri.
不错
Great.
多谢
Thanks.
对了 你们可能需要点子弹
Oh, yeah, right. You probably need some more ammunition.
抱歉 我问一下
Uh, excuse me for asking,
你这算不算是给自己的死刑定了个期呢
But aren't you kind of signing your own death warrant?
我是指 在我们跟恶魔决斗后输了的话
I mean, what happens to you.
你会怎么样
If we go up against the devil and lose?
第一 他会把我们全扫光
Number one … he's gonna wipe us all out anyway.
第二 你们离开这里之后
Two … after you leave here,
那些那些无处不在的约会还等着我继续长期旅行
I go on an extended vacation to all points nowhere.
第三 不如你们别失败呢
And three … how about you don't miss?!
可以吗
Okay?!
低能们
Morons!
好吧 开始了 大人物
All right, big boy. Let's go.
我好像开始感觉到一些东西了
I think I'm starting to feel something.
这是个套 对不
It's got to be a trap, right?
萨姆·温彻斯特与恶魔产生了信任危机啊
Sam Winchester having trust issues with a demon.
也好 亡羊补牢 为时不晚
Well, better late than never.
十分感谢你一如既往的支持
Yeah, and thank you again for your continued support.
不客气
You're welcome.
听着 不管是不是套
And, you know, trap or no trap,
我们这都是在滚雪球 开始了就得继续 对不
We got a snowball's chance, we got to take it, right?
嗯 我想也是
Yeah, I suppose.
况且 我觉得这不一定是个套
Besides, I'm not sure it is a trap.
看看这些
Check it out.
迦太基就像是棵带着被揭示预兆的
Carthage is lit up like a christmas tree.
圣诞树
With revelation omens.
瞧这个
And look at this.
周日以来有六起失踪人口
There's been six missing persons reported.
被报了出来
In town since sunday.
恶魔应该就在那儿
I think the devil's there.
好吧
Okay.
听着 你仔细想想
Look, when you think about it…
你还是别跟来了
…You can't come with.
迪恩
Dean…
听着 我去找撒旦然后搞定他这个狗杂种
Look, I go get satan and screw the pooch…
好吧
Okay.
我们已经输掉一个不应该输的筹码了
We've lost a game piece that we can take.
可如果你在那的话
But if you're there…
那就等于我们把恶魔皮囊双手奉上了
Then we are handing the devil's vessel right over to him.
这可不太明智了
That's not smart.
我们什么时候做过明智的事儿了
Since when have we ever done anything smart?
我认真的 萨姆
I'm serious, sam.
我也认真的
So am i.
我们不是有过一次教训了吗
Haven't we learned a damn thing?
如果要做这事儿 那我们就一起做
If we're gonna do this, we're gonna do it together.
好吧
Okay.
这主意真是愚蠢到家了
That's a stupid friggin' idea.
老兄 我们在说那个蠢到家的主意呢
Boy. Talk about stupid ideas.
老天爷啊
Good god.
这的确是
True, that.
那么
So…
明天任务艰巨啊
Dangerous misson tomorrow.
我想是时候
Guess it's time to…
吃饭 喝酒 还有 你知道的
Eat, drink, and… You know…
寻欢作乐
Make merry.
你是在说这是地球上的最后一晚了吗
Are you giving me the "last night on earth" speech?
什么
What?
不
No.
不是
要是我就是那意思的话 那 它有用吗
If I was, would, uh… W-would that work?
没有
No.
甜心儿 如果这是我们地球上的最后一晚
Sweetheart, if this is our last night on earth,
那我会和一种叫做
Then I'm going to spend it.
自重的东西一起度过
With a little thing I call "self-respect."
可前提是你得有那东西啊
If you' into that kind of thing.
大家都过来
Everybody, get in here!
该排队喽
It's time for the lineup.
平常的嫌疑犯 站到那个角去
Usual suspects, in the corner.
拜托 鲍比
Oh, come on, bobby.
又没人想照相
Nobody wants their picture taken.
完全同意
Here, here.
闭嘴 你喝的可是我的酒
Shut up. You're drinkin' my beer.
不管怎么说
Anyway…
我得需要点东西来记住你们这些讨厌鬼
I'm gonna need something to remember your sorry asses by.
有个乐天派在这儿可真够棒的
Always good to have an optimist around.
鲍比说的对
Bobby's right.
明天我们就要去猎杀那个恶魔了
Tomorrow we hunt the devil.
这是我们在地球的最后一晚
This is our last night on earth.
你有信号吗
You getting a signal?
啥都没有
No, nothin'.
真是够吓人的
Nice and spooky.
这地方看上去是不是有点空旷啊
Place seem a little empty to you?
我们去警察局看看
We're gonna go check out the pd.
你们呆在这儿看能不能找到别的什么人
You guys stay here see if you can find anybody.
好的
Okay.
听说过有种东西叫门把手吗
Ever heard of a door handle?
当然听说过
Of course I have.
怎么了 卡西
What is it, cass?
这个小镇并不是没人
This town's not empty.
死神们
Reapers.
死神们 就是说不只一个吗
"Reapers"? As in more than one?
他们只有在发生重大灾难的时候
They only gather like this.
才会像这样聚集起来
At times of great catastrophe …
芝加哥大火灾 旧金山地震
Chicago fire, san francisco quake…
庞贝城（因火山爆发而灭城的意大利古都）
Pompeii.
恕我失礼 我要去查清楚他们怎么会在这儿
Excuse me. I need to find out why they're here.
你好啊 兄弟
Hello, brother.
警察局没人
Station's empty.
别的地方也是
So is everything else.
你们看见卡西了吗
Have you seen cass?
什么 他和你们在一起的啊
What? He was with you.
没有 他去找死神了
Nope. He went after the reapers.
死神
Reapers?
他看见死神了吗 在什么地方
He saw reapers? Where?
这个 应该说是 到处都是
Well, kind of… Everywhere.
路西法
Lucifer.
那么 我想你是和温彻斯特兄弟一起来的吧
So, I take it you're here with the winchesters.
我自己来的
I came alone.
忠诚
Loyalty.
在这个时代里这可真是难得的品质了
Such a nice quality to see in this day and age.
是卡西迪奥 对吧
"castiel, " right?
卡西迪奥
Castiel…
有人跟我说你是坐车来的
I'm told you came here in an automobile.
是的
Yes.
那感觉怎么样啊
What was that like?
有点慢
Slow.
受拘谨的
Confining.
你可真够奇怪的
What a peculiar thing you are.
你的皮囊怎么了
What's wrong with your vessel?
是啊
Yes, um…
我觉得尼克有点紧
Nick is wearing a bit thin, I'm afraid.
他不可能一直容纳着我 所以
He can't contain me forever, so…
你
You …
你休想占有萨姆·温切斯特
You are not taking Sam Winchester.
我不会让你得逞的
I won't let you.
卡西迪奥
Castiel.
我不明白你干嘛要跟我对着干
I don't understand why you're fighting me,
还是单枪匹马得来
Off all the angels.
你是拿我开涮吗
You really have to ask?
我叛乱了 被驱逐了
I rebelled. I was cast out.
你也叛变了 也被驱逐了
You rebelled. You were cast out.
天堂里的人个个都巴不得我死
Almost all of heaven wants to see me dead.
如果真如他们所愿了 猜猜会怎么着
And if they succeed, guess what.
你就会晋升为他们眼中的头号大敌
You're their new public enemy number one.
我们现在的处境相同 不管你喜欢与否 所以
We're on the same side, like it or not, so…
干嘛不为自己多考虑考虑呢
Why not just serve your own best interests?
万一你有一天 不得不沦落成我这样呢
Which, in this case, just happen to be mine.
我会一死了之
I'll die first.
我看你确实是离死不远了
I suppose you will.
真是棒极了 我们都在这城里转悠了20分钟了
Well, this is great. We've been in town for 20 minutes.
我想我们的风衣天使没得救了
We've already lost the angel up our sleeve.
你认为 是路西法抓了他吗
You think, uh… You think Lucifer got him?
我也没什么头绪
I don't know what else to think.
嘿 你们几个
There you are.
梅格
Meg!
你们不该来这儿的 帅小伙们
You shouldn't have come here, boys.
是吗 那是我想对你说的话
Yeah? Well, I could say the same thing for you.
别只身过来 小迪
Didn't come here alone, Dean-o.
地狱之犬
Hellhounds!
没错 迪恩 你的最爱
Yeah, Dean … your favorite.
跟我来 帅小伙们
Come on, boys.
我爸爸想见你们
My father wants to see you.
我想我们没空 谢了
I think we'll pass. Thanks.
随便你们
Your call.
是要让事情简单化
You can make this easy,
还是非常非常地复杂化 都在于你们
Or you can make it really, really hard.
你见过我们选简单之路走过了吗
When have you known us to ever make anything easy?
快跑
Run!
迪恩
Dean!
乔 别过来
Jo, stay back!
不
No!
好了 好了 没事了 没事了
All right. Okay, okay, okay.
呼吸 保持呼吸 保持呼吸
Breathe, breathe, breathe.
我没事 没事
I'm fine. I'm fine.
小伙子们 这需要帮手
Boys, need some help here!
快快快 动作快
Go go go…
没事儿的 你会好起来的
It'll be all right. Okay? You're gonna be all right.
谢谢
Thank you.
她撑得住吗
How's she holding up?
那些盐线撑得住吗
The salt lines are holding up.
现在绝对没问题
Safe for now.
是啊 安全得像个瓮中之鳖
Yeah, safe or trapped like rats.
嘿 你也听到梅格说的话了吧
Hey, you heard Meg.
他父亲在这儿
Her father's here.
这是我们的一次机会 萨姆
This is our one shot, Sammy.
无论如何 我们都要抓住机会
We got to take it, no matter what.
我们走
There we go.
萨姆 过来帮帮我 行吗
Sam, some help here, please?
你所拨打的号码是空号
The number you dialed is unavailable.
请你查询后再拨
Please try your call again…
该死的 臭小子
Damn it, boys.
这里是福克斯三角洲的KC5号 请讲
Kc5 Fox Delta Oscar, go ahead.
鲍比 我是迪恩 我们有麻烦了
Bobby, it's Dean. We got problems.
没事的 孩子 这就是我在这里的原因
It's okay, boy. That's why I'm here.
大家都还好吧
Is everyone all right?
不
No.
鲍比 乔的情况很糟
It's Jo. Bobby, it's pretty bad.
好的 收到
Okay. Copy that.
现在我们考虑接下来做什么
So now we figure what we do next.
鲍比 我想她不能
Bobby, I don't think she's …
我说了 接下来做什么 迪恩
I said, "what do we do next, " Dean.
好的
Right.
Okay. Right.
现在 告诉我你们的情况
Now… Tell me what you got.
在卡西失踪之前 他说过有多少死神吗
Before he went missing, did Cass say how many reapers?
我不知道
I-I don't know.
他说了很多 我想
He said a lot of things, I guess.
我是说 死神数目重要吗
I mean, does the number matter?
详细描述恶魔 迪恩
Devil's in the details, Dean.
鲍比 我是艾伦
Bobby, it's Ellen.
卡西迪奥看死神时的样子
The way he was looking,
还有他目光所到之处的数目
The number of places Castiel's eyes went,
我得说我们说的是超过一打死神 也许更多
I'd say we're talking over a dozen reapers … probably more.
我不喜欢那种声音
I do not like the sound of that.
没人喜欢那声音 但是 鲍比
Nobody likes the sound of that, Bobby, but …
那 那究竟是什么状况
What … what does that sound like?
听起来像是死亡骑士 孩子
It sounds like death, son.
我觉得路西法准备在镇上举行仪式
I think satan's in town to work a ritual.
他想要释放死亡骑士
I think he's planning to unleash death.
还能有比这家伙还有缴税
You mean, like, as in this dude and.
更确定一点的事情吗
taxes are the only sure thing?
我是指死亡骑士 天启四骑士中的灰色骑士
As in death … the horseman, the pale rider in the flesh.
你刚才说「解放」
"Unleash"?
我是指 死亡不是无处不在吗
I mean, h-hasn't death been tromping all over the place?
我是说 见鬼 我不都死了好几回吗了
I mean, hell, I died several times myself.
这次不同
Not this guy.
这是 是地狱男爵
This is … this is the angel of death,
可以说是死神之父
Big daddy reaper.
他被拘禁在深深的地底
They keep this guy chained in a box 600 feet under.
上一次把他上来的时候 诺亚造了一艘船呢
Last time they hauled him up, Noah was building a boat.
难怪那鬼地方满是死神
That's why the place is crawling with reapers.
他们在等候老大的出现
They're waiting on the big boss to show.
有什么好消息吗
You have any other good news?
某种意义上来说是的
Well, in a manner of speaking.
你们走后 我一直在研究迦太基的资料
I've been researching carthage since you've been gone,
试图查清路西法的目的
Trying to suss out what the devil might want there.
你刚才所说的情况
What you just said drops the last.
正好解开了最后的谜团
piece of the puzzle in place.
召唤地狱男爵的条件是
The angel of death must be brought into this world.
午夜时间 进行一场可怕的大屠杀
At midnight through a place of awful carnage.
回顾到内战时期
Now, back during the civil war,
迦太基发生过一场大战
There was a battle in carthage …
这场战斗极其惨烈
A battle so intense,
因此战士们将其称之为「地狱之战」
The soldiers called it "the battle of hellhole."
大屠杀发生在哪里
Where'd the massacre go down?
那个地方现在是威廉·贾思博的农场
On the land of William Jasper's farm.
温彻斯特一伙人被我牵制住了
I got the Winchesters pinned down …
至少目前为止
For now, at least.
我要对他们做些什么
What should I do with them?
不用管他们了
Leave them alone.
我不明白 你确定吗
I-I'm sorry, but are you sure?
我们不是应该
Shouldn't we …
相信我 孩子
Trust me, child.
万事皆有因
Everything happens for a reason.
卡西迪奥
Well, Castiel…
你还有时间
You have some time.
来改变主意
Time to change your mind.
既然我们知道了恶魔会在何时
So, now we know where the devil's gonna be,
何地出现 我们还有科尔特
We know when, and we have the colt.
没错
Yeah.
只不过要在午夜前赶到农场
We just have to get past… Eight or so hellhounds.
需要甩掉八多条地狱犬
And get to the farm by midnight.
是啊 我们还得先把乔和艾伦
Yeah, and that's after we get Jo.
送出这个鬼地方
and Ellen the hell out of town.
这可不容易
Won't be easy.
用担架吗
Stretcher?
我去看看我们有些什么
I'll see what we got.
别说了
Stop.
伙计们 别说了
Guys, stop.
我们能现实点吗
Can we, uh, be realistic about this, please?
我的腿无法移动
I can't move my legs.
也不能被转移
I can't be moved.
我的肠子靠绷带支撑着
My guts are being held in by an ace bandage.
我们必须
We got to…
我们必须先处理这儿的问题
We got to get our priorities straight here.
首先 我哪儿也不能去
Number one … I'm not going anywhere.
- 乔安娜·贝丝 别用这种语气说话 - 妈妈
- Joanna beth, you stop talking like that - Mom.
我无法战斗
I can't fight.
不能走路
I can't walk.
但我还能做点什么
But I can do something.
这里有丙烷 导火线 石盐和铁钉
We've got propane, wiring, rock salt, iron nails …
对我们来说足够了
Everything we need.
用来做什么
Everything we need?
做一个炸弹 萨姆
To build a bomb, sam.
不
No.
乔 别这样
Jo…No.
你有其他主意吗
You got another plan?
还有其他更好的主意吗
You got any other plan?
外面充斥着地狱犬 迪恩
Those are hellhounds out there, dean.
它们熟悉我们的气味
They've got all of our scents.
那些狗杂种会一直追你到天涯海角
Those bitches will never stop coming after you.
我们让它们进来
We let the dogs in,
你们可以从屋顶爬出去
You guys hit the roof,
抓住机会冲向旁边的楼
Make a break for the building next over,
我留在这里引爆
And I can wait here with my finger on the button.
把那些狗炸得不成样子
Rip those mutts a new one.
或者至少让你们有几分钟的领先
Or at least get you a few minutes' head start, anyway.
不 我不会让你这样的
No, i… I won't let you.
这是我们来这儿的原因 不是吗
This is why we're here, right?
如果我可以给恶魔一击
If I can get us a shot on the devil…
迪恩 我们不得不这样做
Dean, we have to take it.
不
No!
不是
That's not …
妈妈
Mom.
这也许真的是你
This might literally be.
最后一次拿我当大人一样对待了
Your last chance to treat me like an adult.
你也许希望这样的
You might want to take it.
你们听见她说的了
You heard her.
开始准备吧
Get to work.
好 就是这个
Okay, this is it.
我们将在另一个世界相会
I'll see you on the other side.
这是迟早的事儿
Probably sooner than later.
还是晚点吧
Make it later.
好吧
Okay.
妈妈 不要
Mom, no.
得有人把它们放进来
Somebody's got to let them in.
就像你说的 你动不了
And like you said, you're not moving.
你还有我 乔
You got me, Jo.
你是对的
And you're right.
这很重要
This is important.
但我不会我丢下你一个人
But I will not leave you here alone.
迪恩
Dean?
走吧 孩子们
Get goin' now, boys.
艾伦
Ellen?
快走
I said go.
还有 迪恩
And, Dean…
打败他们
Kick it in the ass.
要一下一个
Don't miss.
我永远爱你 宝贝
I will always love you, baby.
我
I…
宝贝
Honey?
乔
Jo…
没事的
It's okay.
我的好女儿
That's my good girl.
滚回地狱去吧 你们这些丑陋的疯狗
You can go straight back to hell, you ugly bitch!
我想我们知道镇上的那些人怎么了
I guess we know what happened to some of the townspeople.
好
Okay.
怎么样
Last words?
我觉得我没事儿
I think I'm good.
是的 我也是
Yeah. Me too.
这儿什么也没有
Here goes nothin'.
你想见我
You wanted to see me?!
萨姆 在这儿你不需要那把枪
Well, Sam, you don't need that gun here.
你知道我永远不会伤害你
You know I'd never hurt you.
不会的
Not really.
是吗
Yeah?
那么 我会伤害你
Well, I'd hurt you.
去死吧
So suck it.
你是从哪里得到枪的
Where did you get that?
现在
Now…
我们说到哪了
Where were we?
别太难过了 萨姆
Don't feel too bad, Sam.
世界万物只有五样东西
There's only five things in all of creation.
是这枪打不死的
That that gun can't kill,
而我正好是其中之一
And…I just happen to be one of them.
给我一点儿时间 我就快完成了
But if you give me a minute, I'm almost done.
我没期望你此时此刻就答应
I don't suppose you'd just say "yes" right here and now?
结束这无聊的对话吧
End this whole tiresome discussion?
太疯狂了 是吧
That's crazy, right?
这永远不会发生
It's never gonna happen!
我不知道 萨姆
Oh, I don't know, Sam.
我觉得会的
I think it will.
我举的这不久就会发生
I think it'll happen soon …
6个月之内
Within six months.
我觉得会在发生在底特律
And I think it'll happen… In Detroit.
听着 你这狗日的东西
You listen to me, you son of a bitch.
我要亲手杀了你
I'm gonna kill you myself.
懂吗
You understand me?
我要把你的心挖出来
I'm going to rip your heart out!
这样很好 萨姆
That's good, Sam.
燃起心中的怒火
You keep fanning that fire in your belly …
所有被压抑着的怒火
All that pent-up rage.
正是我要的
I'm gonna need it.
你干了什么
What did you do?
你对这个镇干了什么
What did you do to this town?
哦 我对这个镇很大方
Oh, I was very generous with this town.
一个强壮的人符着一个恶魔
One demon for every able-bodied man.
其他人呢
And the rest of them?
在这下面
In there.
我知道很可怕 但是
I know … it's awful. But…
天启骑士们的需求很大
These horsemen are so demanding.
所以就 女人和小孩优先
So it was… Women and children first.
我知道你怎看待想我的 萨姆
I know what you must think of me, sam.
但我必须这么做
But I have to do this.
必须的
I have to.
不光是你 所有人都应该理解
You, of all people, should understand.
你什么意思
Well, what's that supposed to mean?
我是个儿子
I was a son.
是个弟弟 像你一样
A brother, like you.
一个弟弟
A younger brother.
我爱我的兄长
And I had an older brother who I loved.
确切的说是崇拜
Idolized, in fact.
有一天 我去找他
And one day, I went to him.
我求他支持我
And I begged him to stand with me,
但是米迦勒
And michael…
米迦勒没有这样做
Michael turned on me.
说我是个怪人
Called me a freak.
一个怪物
A monster.
然后他打败了我
And then he beat me down.
只因为我与他们不一样
All because I was different.
因为我有自己的想法
Because I had a mind of my own.
说说看 萨姆
Tell me something, sam.
听起来耳熟吗
Any of this sound familiar?
不管怎样
Anyway…
你要等我一下 快到午夜了
You'll have to excuse me. Midnight is calling.
我得完成一个仪式
And I have a ritual to finish.
哪也别去
Don't go anywhere.
你也哪都去不了
Not that you could if you would.
现在跟着我说
Now, repeat after me.
我们献上自己的生命 血液 灵魂
We offer up our lives, blood, souls…
来作为贡品
…To complete this tribute.
作为贡品
怎么
What?
他们是恶魔而已
They're just demons.
你看起来挺高兴的
You seem pleased.
我们要赢了
We're gonna win.
你能感觉到吗
Can you feel it?
你们的那些天使输掉了整个世界
You cloud-hopping pansies lost the whole damn universe.
路西法要接管天堂了
Lucifer's gonna take over heaven.
我们要去天堂了 天使
We're goin' to heaven, clarence.
不一定吧
Strange.
我从克劳力那里听到的消息
Because I heard a different theory.
可是完全不同
From a demon named Crowley.
你不了解Crowley
You don't know Crowley.
他觉得路西法只是利用恶魔
He believes that lucifer is just using demons.
去开启末日
To achieve an end.
之后
And that…
他一旦达到了目的
…Once he does…
就会灭了你们
…He'll destroy you all.
你错了
You're wrong.
路西法是我们的父亲
Lucifer is the father of our race …
我们的缔造者
Our creator.
你们的上帝可能游手好闲 但我们的
Your god may be a deadbeat, but mine …
但是我们的却就在这世上
Mine walks the earth.
你偷袭不了恶魔 对吗
You can't gank demons, can you?
你被你们家除名了
You're cut off from the home office,
那些能力就用不了了
And you ain't got the juice.
那么你还能干什么呢 你这没用的东西
So, what can you do, you impotent sap?
可以干这个
I can do this.
你好啊 死亡骑士
Oh, hello, death.
当局宣布
The government has declared.
保尔丁县进入紧急状态
A state of emergency for paulding county,
包括马里恩 斐尔维尔和迦太基镇
Including the towns of marion, fetterville, and carthage.
根据报道 暴风警报已开启
The storm system has reportedly touched off.
这一区域存在很多龙卷风
A number of tornadoes in the area.
死亡人数还无法估计
Death tolls have yet to be estimated.
但州政府预计生命和财产损失
But state officials expect the loss of life and property.
非常严重
To be staggering.